

# **Profile**

Completely immersed into the world of Computer Science and programming. Backend developer and novice DevOps at IT start-up. Fourth year BSc student on academic leave, Yandex.Practicum graduate, ICAgile Certified Professional. Total experience in programming: 4 years.

# **Employment History**

## DevOps Engineer, Product Lab, Moscow

DECEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

Configured needed infrastructure (physical machines, VPC, firewall policies) using cloud services. Created not complicated CI/CD development and production pipelines using containerization, optimized some of the development processes (setups, build, database migrations). Used few open source projects and had lots of work with networking and Shell scripting.

#### Backend Developer, Product Lab, Moscow

AUGUST 2022 - PRESENT

Was responsible for multi-tenant database and backend architectural design of SaaS, as well as its' REST API functionality, aimed to apply OKRs methodology. Tried slightly different varieties of instruments, one of which subsequently has become the tech stack used in the project.

# Education

# BSc, National Research University "Higher School of Economics", Moscow

JULY 2019 - PRESENT

Fourth year BSc "<u>Business-Informatics</u>" student, currently on 2-year academic leave. Cyber Security <u>minor</u> graduate.

# Internships

#### Intern at IT Department, Product Lab, Moscow

JULY 2022 - JULY 2022

Was initially introduced to work in teams and such methodologies as Scrum and Kanban. Reviewed and proposed UML designs.

# Courses

#### C++ Developer, Yandex.Practicum

NOVEMBER 2020 - NOVEMBER 2021

#### ICAgile Certified Professional, Product Lab

SEPTEMBER 2022 - SEPTEMBER 2022

#### Hebrew Language (B1), Uplan "Ahva", Rishon Lezion

DECEMBER 2022 - JUNE 2023

### **Details**

Tel Aviv

Israel

+972 52 620 1269

kholodilinm@gmail.com

DATE OF BIRTH

04.09.2000

### Links

GitHub

**Telegram** 

LinkedIn

#### Skills

JavaScript (Express.js, Sequelize.js)

C++ (std, Cmake, PB)

Linux (Bash, Shell, Make)

Computer Networking

**GCP** 

Git

Windows

Docker

SQL

Python

# Languages

Russian

English (IELTS 7.5)

Hebrew